<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Georgina (Georgy) Falster on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://georgyfalster.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Georgina (Georgy) Falster on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://georgyfalster.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://georgyfalster.github.io/about_me/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 16:30:12 +1030</pubDate>
      <guid>https://georgyfalster.github.io/about_me/</guid>
      <description>clouds restore in rain&#xA;the exhalations of the land and sea -H. W. Longfellow&#xA;This lovely snippet from Longfellow&amp;rsquo;s prelude to Michael Angelo describes the water cycle: the movement of water around the Earth.&#xA;I am a climate scientist, tackling the same topic but using science. With my research I work to understand the huge range of factors influencing when, where, and why rain falls in different places around the world - and how that is changing because of climate change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>https://georgyfalster.github.io/updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 16:30:12 +1030</pubDate>
      <guid>https://georgyfalster.github.io/updates/</guid>
      <description>02 May 2025 I am pleased to have become a member of the Environment Institute at The University of Adelaide. The Institute brings together researchers across ecology, biology, biodiversity, anthropology, climate science and more to tackle the environmental challenges facing Australia. I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to working within such a multi-disciplinary group.&#xA;I recently wrote a blog post for the Institute, describing my Australian drought research: you can read the blog post here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://georgyfalster.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 16:30:12 +1030</pubDate>
      <guid>https://georgyfalster.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Publications on Google Scholar Link to my Google Scholar profile&#xA;Published Journal Articles Cho, P., G. Falster, D. Bolster, M. Berke, M. Müller. 2025. Influence of the Indian Walker Circulation on δ18OP and precipitation variability in the Indian Ocean Basin. JGR Atmospheres 130: e2025JD043840. Link to publication. Holgate, C., G. Falster, Z. Gillett, P. Goswami, M. Grant, S. Hobeichi, D. Hoffman, X. Jiang, C. Jin, X. Lu, M. Mu, J. Page, T.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>https://georgyfalster.github.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 16:30:12 +1030</pubDate>
      <guid>https://georgyfalster.github.io/cv/</guid>
      <description>Full curriculum vitae Current Affiliation DECRA Fellow The University of Adelaide&#xA;Using climate model simulations, rainwater isotopes, weather observations, and tree ring isotopes for a holistic understanding of Australian droughts and how they are changing.&#xA;Previous Affiliations ARC Centre of Excellence for Climate Extremes postdoctoral fellow The Australian National University&#xA;I combined information from modern observational data and model simulations to better understand the dynamics and drivers of Australian drought.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://georgyfalster.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 16:30:12 +1030</pubDate>
      <guid>https://georgyfalster.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Journalists: please see my Scimex profile.&#xA;Otherwise, my contact details are available from my institutional profile.&#xA;Here I am with my favourite instrument - the Picarro L2140-i cavity ring-down spectroscopy water isotope analyser.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
