<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Georgina (Georgy) Falster on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://georgyfalster.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Georgina (Georgy) Falster on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://georgyfalster.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://georgyfalster.github.io/about_me/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 16:30:12 +1030</pubDate>
      <guid>https://georgyfalster.github.io/about_me/</guid>
      <description>clouds restore in rain&#xA;the exhalations of the land and sea -H. W. Longfellow&#xA;This snippet from Longfellow&amp;rsquo;s prelude to Michael Angelo describes the water cycle: the movement of water around the Earth.&#xA;I am a climate scientist, tackling the same topic but using science. I try to understand the huge range of factors influencing when, where, and why rain falls in different places around the world - and how that is changing because of climate change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>https://georgyfalster.github.io/updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 16:30:12 +1030</pubDate>
      <guid>https://georgyfalster.github.io/updates/</guid>
      <description>21 January 2026 New open access paper and datasets! Just published in Hydrology and Earth System Sciences: the stable isotopic composition of monthly precipitation over the Australian continent from 1962-2023, estimated using random forest models.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m hoping this will be a handy resource for a lot of people working in fields where it is useful to have time-resolved precipitation isotope information - biologists, archaeologists, ecologists, hydrologists, forensic scientists, and of course palaeoclimatologists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://georgyfalster.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 16:30:12 +1030</pubDate>
      <guid>https://georgyfalster.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Publications on Google Scholar Link to my Google Scholar profile&#xA;Published Journal Articles Abram, N., N. Maher, S. Perkins-Kirkpatrick, G. Falster, T. Hughes, K. Meissnerm L. Slater, A. King, A. Pitman, G. Moon, W. Morgan. 2025. Quantifying the regional to global climate impacts of individual fossil fuel projects to inform decision-making. npj Climate Action 4: Article 92. Link to publication. Vaiglova, P., H. Kierdorf, C. Witzel, G. Falster, R. Joannes-Boyau, Y.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>https://georgyfalster.github.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 16:30:12 +1030</pubDate>
      <guid>https://georgyfalster.github.io/cv/</guid>
      <description>Full curriculum vitae Current Affiliation DECRA Fellow The University of Adelaide&#xA;Using climate model simulations, rainwater isotopes, weather observations, and tree ring isotopes for a holistic understanding of Australian droughts and how they are changing.&#xA;Major Extramural Grant Funding L&amp;rsquo;Oréal-UNESCO For Women in Science Fellowship ($25000, sole investigator) [2025] Australian Research Council Discovery Early Career Researcher Award (DECRA) DE250100071 Quantifying Australia’s long-term risk of rainfall extremes ($438335, sole investigator) [2025] National Computational Infrastructure (NCI) Merit Allocation Scheme The role of Indo-Pacific SST variability in global drought occurrence (1000 kSU, equivalent to $40000, chief investigator) [2025] Previous Affiliations ARC Centre of Excellence for Climate Extremes postdoctoral fellow The Australian National University</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://georgyfalster.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 16:30:12 +1030</pubDate>
      <guid>https://georgyfalster.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Journalists: please see my Scimex profile.&#xA;Otherwise, my contact details are available from my institutional profile.&#xA;Here I am with my favourite instrument - the Picarro L2140-i cavity ring-down spectroscopy water isotope analyser.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
