<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Georgina (Georgy) Falster on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://georgyfalster.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Georgina (Georgy) Falster on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://georgyfalster.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://georgyfalster.github.io/about_me/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 16:30:12 +1030</pubDate>
      <guid>https://georgyfalster.github.io/about_me/</guid>
      <description>clouds restore in rain&#xA;the exhalations of the land and sea -H. W. Longfellow&#xA;This snippet from Longfellow&amp;rsquo;s prelude to Michael Angelo describes the water cycle: the movement of water around the Earth.&#xA;I am a climate scientist, tackling the same topic but using science. I try to understand the huge range of factors influencing when, where, and why rain falls in different places around the world - and how that is changing because of climate change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>https://georgyfalster.github.io/updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 16:30:12 +1030</pubDate>
      <guid>https://georgyfalster.github.io/updates/</guid>
      <description>22 September 2025 In a truly bizarre turn of events, I am exceptionally lucky to be one of the four recipients of a 2025 Australia/NZ L&amp;rsquo;Oréal-UNESCO For Women In Science Fellowship. These awards - as well as being prestigious, generous, and highly competitive - come with a fancy award ceremony and the opportunity to mentor the next generation of scientists through the For Girls in Science forum.&#xA;The grant comes at a perfect time as I&amp;rsquo;m waging a one-girl campaign to establish my own little holistic climate research lab - I&amp;rsquo;ll use the money to buy tree ring analysis equipment as well as to visit collaborators and head to San Francisco for AGU in 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://georgyfalster.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 16:30:12 +1030</pubDate>
      <guid>https://georgyfalster.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Publications on Google Scholar Link to my Google Scholar profile&#xA;Published Journal Articles Vaiglova, P., H. Kierdorf, C. Witzel, G. Falster, R. Joannes-Boyau, Y. Wang, J. Wu, I. Williams, B. Knowles, Y. Wu, P. Bangsgaard, L. Yeomans, T. Richter, H. Darabi. 2025. Transport of animals underpinned ritual feasting at the onset of the Neolithic in southwestern Asia. Communications Earth &amp;amp; Environment 6: Article 519. Link to publication. Cho, P., G. Falster, D.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>https://georgyfalster.github.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 16:30:12 +1030</pubDate>
      <guid>https://georgyfalster.github.io/cv/</guid>
      <description>Full curriculum vitae Current Affiliation DECRA Fellow The University of Adelaide&#xA;Using climate model simulations, rainwater isotopes, weather observations, and tree ring isotopes for a holistic understanding of Australian droughts and how they are changing.&#xA;Previous Affiliations ARC Centre of Excellence for Climate Extremes postdoctoral fellow The Australian National University&#xA;I combined information from modern observational data and model simulations to better understand the dynamics and drivers of Australian drought.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://georgyfalster.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 16:30:12 +1030</pubDate>
      <guid>https://georgyfalster.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Journalists: please see my Scimex profile.&#xA;Otherwise, my contact details are available from my institutional profile.&#xA;Here I am with my favourite instrument - the Picarro L2140-i cavity ring-down spectroscopy water isotope analyser.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
