<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Georgina (Georgy) Falster on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://georgyfalster.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Georgina (Georgy) Falster on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://georgyfalster.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://georgyfalster.github.io/about_me/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 16:30:12 +1030</pubDate>
      <guid>https://georgyfalster.github.io/about_me/</guid>
      <description>I am a climate scientist. I try to understand what Earth&amp;rsquo;s climate would look like now, if not for human activities like greenhouse gas and aerosol emissions. Part of that involves understanding modern climate dynamics. Another part involves studying climate variability in the time before the Industrial Revolution. Figuring out the difference between those two things helps us to understand how and why Earth&amp;rsquo;s climate is changing today, and hence how it might change in the future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>https://georgyfalster.github.io/updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 16:30:12 +1030</pubDate>
      <guid>https://georgyfalster.github.io/updates/</guid>
      <description>19 December 2024 I&amp;rsquo;m honoured to have been selected by Science and Technology Australia to participate in the 2025/2026 Superstars of STEM programme.&#xA;The programme aims to break down gender assumptions about who can work in STEM (Science, Technology, Engineering, Mathematics) and boost media visibility of women and non-binary STEM experts. After a long selection process, myself and 59 other STEM professionals from across Australia - across fields, industries, and career stages - will be supported in appearing as expert commentators on Australian media, on platforms from news and panel shows to social media and public events.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://georgyfalster.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 16:30:12 +1030</pubDate>
      <guid>https://georgyfalster.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Publications on Google Scholar Link to my Google Scholar profile&#xA;Published Journal Articles Falster, G., S. Coats, N. Abram. 2024. &amp;ldquo;How unusual was Australia&amp;rsquo;s 2017-2019 Tinderbox Drought?&amp;rdquo;. Weather and Climate Extremes 46. Link to publication. Falster, G., N. Wright, N. Abram. A. Ukkola, B. Henley. 2024. &amp;ldquo;Potential for historically unprecedented Australian droughts from natural variability and climate change&amp;rdquo;. Hydrology and Earth System Sciences 28: 1383-1401. Link to publication. Devanand, A., G.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>https://georgyfalster.github.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 16:30:12 +1030</pubDate>
      <guid>https://georgyfalster.github.io/cv/</guid>
      <description>Full curriculum vitae Current Affiliation Postdoctoral fellow (and soon-to-be ARC DECRA Fellow) The Australian National University&#xA;I combine information from modern observational data, palaeoclimate proxy data, and model simulations to better understand the dynamics and drivers of Australian drought.&#xA;Previous Affiliation Postdoctoral research associate Washington University in St. Louis&#xA;I used water isotope observations, proxy records, and model simulations to investigate forced and internal variability in ocean-atmosphere circulation.&#xA;Education PhD (awarded April 2019) The University of Adelaide, Australia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://georgyfalster.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 16:30:12 +1030</pubDate>
      <guid>https://georgyfalster.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Journalists: please see my Scimex profile.&#xA;Otherwise, my contact details are available from my institutional profile.&#xA;Here I am with my favourite instrument - the Picarro L2140-i cavity ring-down spectroscopy water isotope analyser.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
